<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CharacterInfo</string>
    <string name="maki">
        Maki is a person surrounded with mystery, but with quite strange temper. Because of the events that happened in his life,
        Maki had develop strong resistance of receiving help from others as well as not allowing people to get closer to him due to the death of people close to him -his parents,
        Sawamura Satoshi (his legal guardian), Suzuki, Amachi and later on, Aoki\'s elder sister and brother-in-law.
        Maki was heavily affected by their deaths and often blaming himself for unable to protect people,
        especially if they are involved with the cases he handle.
        These caused heavy trauma to him that led him into his mental breakdown,
        witnessed by Okabe prior the start of the story.
        His expression usually calm and cool with strict personality,
        however he treats people coldly or even harsh;
        this usually happened when the people he cared for trying to do something reckless that could cause harm to them. This usually happened to Aoki as he tends to act reckless and hurts himself.
        He is calm and restrained, not reveal
        his inner feelings except very few people who're close to him as well as moody. He has sharp thinking, perceptive, precisely handling the investigation hundred percent whole-hardheartedly,
        and full of vicious. However, mostly new comers resigned from Section Nine due to their incompatibility to work with Maki and his personality. Maki is a very hard-working person, but he also a very sound sleeper. Sometimes he will grip someone in his sleep and refused to let go. This situation happened when Aoki tried to wake him up and had to call for help to release himself from the sleeping director.
    </string>
    <string name="lalouch">

        Lelouch is a highly intelligent individual who is also calm, sophisticated, and arrogant due to his aristocratic upbringing. While at school, Lelouch conducts himself as a sociable, likeable, and often easygoing student. However, this is really a mask to hide his true nature. While as Zero his true nature is expressed. His charisma and beliefs in justice gain him the trust and respect of many soldiers and leaders.

Lelouch is known for having a very stoic personality. He never cared about schoolwork, seeing the entire thing as trivial, even though his high intelligence would make it easy for him. At one point, Shirley stated that if Lelouch applied himself in school, he could get high grades. He enjoys seeking out challenges, often playing chess against nobility. In general, Lelouch takes most day-to-day affairs with open disinterest, often not even noticing the affection of others, especially Shirley, his fellow classmate. He has a strong dislike for nobles, viewing them as tepid and "overprivileged parasites."

In battle, Lelouch is very cold and tactical. He is willing to sacrifice civilians and soldiers alike, if that is what it takes to achieve the objective. In the battle at Narita, when he created a landslide that wiped out most of the enemy forces, and indirectly, several civilians in the town below, he brushed off the civilian casualties as a simple "mathematical overestimation." He did have second thoughts when he learned that one of them was Shirley's father, but he accepted that there will always be consequences for all of his actions. He also saw no problem with collapsing a large portion of Tokyo, resulting in countless military and civilian casualties.

Many characters have noted that Lelouch is quite selfish, as his desire to remake the world into what he wants it to be comes from his desire to avenge his mother's apparent death and Nunnally's sake, however in time he realizes that this goal is not just for them, but for the entire world.

Despite his cold, calculating demeanor, and ruthlessness in battle, he can be a rather compassionate person to his friends and loved ones. To Nunnally, he is a loving older brother, and to Suzaku, a loyal friend, despite the fact that the two are enemies. Lelouch, at first glance, seems to have relatively little concern for the well-being of his subordinates, but in reality, he does care about them, seeing them as valuable allies. Though he has shown preference on occasion especially with Kallen.

    </string>
    <string name="toua">Tokuchi is usually seen as a laid-back, disrespectful person. He doesn\'t seem to be bothered by ordering around others or being trash talked to. He is very bold, as demonstrated when he creates an outrageous contract with the Lycaon\'s owner, Tsuneo Saikawa,
        and orders the Lycaon\'s manager, Yuuzaburou Mihara, to light his cigarette. He is also shown to have a somewhat kind personality when he agrees with Kojima that he had thrown a beanball, when in actuality Tokuchi had pitched in the strike zone and Kojima had stepped in the zone.
        After the act, he tells Kojima to take his bat and break his right arm,
        to which Kojima says that he never said he was going to break his arm, and asks him to join the Lycaons.

Tokuchi was called an \'outrageous rookie\' for taking Yoshida out of the defense during the game against the Eagles. He is also not polite nor considerate enough to restrain himself from provoking his opponent. In fact, it seems to be a favorite tactic of his.
        He was also not scared to use any means necessary to get what he wanted; he intentionally pitched a dangerous ball to a batter to get ejected from the game with the Eagles.

Tokuchi is also extremely perceptive, and is accustomed to various ways of cheating and deceit involved in baseball. Many of his abilities in this area are most likely due to his background, being an extremely successful gambler.
        This is demonstrated in many ways, such as the countless times Saikawa, the Lycaon's owner, has attempted to sabotage Tokuchi to garner more money. Tokuchi has seen through all of it, and earned even more in the process.

Tokuchi is almost never flustered. Even when he had runs stacked against him in the three consecutive Mariner vs Lycaon games, he calmly figured out a way to negate the runs while gaining some by himself, making use of the rain and pretending to turn the game into a no-game. In the process,
        the Mariners became distraught and were only concerned about the time, while the Lycaons made a turnaround in the confusion.

However, in the latest chapters coming out at this time, Takami, the ace of the Mariners, has appeared to have figured out a working way to counter Tokuchi's abilities. In chapter 154, Tokuchi actually seems to be stressed, and sweat shows on his face. This shows that he can indeed become worried, even with his dominating presence of confidence.
</string>

    <string name="johan">On the surface, Johan is a well-mannered, charismatic and compassionate young man. He possesses a myriad of favorable traits and can easily overwhelm individuals with his seemingly flawless nature, as seen with Hans Georg Schuwald, who describes him as being not of this world. This makes it easy for him to make new allies and manipulate them into doing various deeds for him. With such skill in creating this facade of perfection and pureness, Johan can hide his true motives with ease.
Within this contrived exterior, however, Johan callously delivers destruction and suffering to those who happen to fall prey to his schemes. Even before his tenure at Kinderheim 511, Johan still exhibits psychopathic tendencies. For example, most of his murders, both in childhood and adulthood, have been premeditated and calculated Many of Johan\'s beliefs run consistent with nihilism, as he does not see any meaning to life. He claims, "Most of this universe is 'death' anyway," and that to the universe, "most lives are just specks in a corner of the earth, gone in a flash".[41]

Johan also has a tendency to make his victims experience the worst possible loss and suffering rather than actually killing them himself; this experience often leads to the victims killing themselves, however. Helmut Wolf is a prime example of this; instead of simply being killed, Wolf is forced to watch as all of his close relatives and acquaintances die, one after another, all so he can feel what Johan felt, solitude.

The root of Johan's actions is unknown. Although he was sent to the experimental orphanage of Kinderheim 511, Hartmann informs Tenma that, "[Kinderheim 511] couldn't possibly create a masterpiece like him! Neither of his parents seemed to suffer from psychopathy or any other mental illnesses. Anna, despite being the twin to experience the horrible events at the Red Rose Mansion, turns out to be a genuinely loving and caring person. However, while she is able to suppress her memories of the Red Rose Mansion, Johan takes them as his own, coming to believe that he was the one who experienced them. After the Ruhenheim massacre, while convalescing in a state hospital from his second operation, Johan reveals to Tenma, through unknown means, his memory of his mother's decision, revealing that the memory affected him profoundly.
</string>
</resources>
