<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CharacterInfo</string>
    <string name="maki">
        Maki is a person surrounded with mystery, but with quite strange temper. Because of the events that happened in his life,
        Maki had develop strong resistance of receiving help from others as well as not allowing people to get closer to him due to the death of people close to him -his parents,
        Sawamura Satoshi (his legal guardian), Suzuki, Amachi and later on, Aoki\'s elder sister and brother-in-law.
        Maki was heavily affected by their deaths and often blaming himself for unable to protect people,
        especially if they are involved with the cases he handle.
        These caused heavy trauma to him that led him into his mental breakdown,
        witnessed by Okabe prior the start of the story.
        His expression usually calm and cool with strict personality,
        however he treats people coldly or even harsh;
        this usually happened when the people he cared for trying to do something reckless that could cause harm to them. This usually happened to Aoki as he tends to act reckless and hurts himself.
        He is calm and restrained, not reveal
        his inner feelings except very few people who're close to him as well as moody. He has sharp thinking, perceptive, precisely handling the investigation hundred percent whole-hardheartedly,
        and full of vicious. However, mostly new comers resigned from Section Nine due to their incompatibility to work with Maki and his personality. Maki is a very hard-working person, but he also a very sound sleeper. Sometimes he will grip someone in his sleep and refused to let go. This situation happened when Aoki tried to wake him up and had to call for help to release himself from the sleeping director.
    </string>
    <string name="lalouch">

        Lelouch is a highly intelligent individual who is also calm, sophisticated, and arrogant due to his aristocratic upbringing. While at school, Lelouch conducts himself as a sociable, likeable, and often easygoing student. However, this is really a mask to hide his true nature. While as Zero his true nature is expressed. His charisma and beliefs in justice gain him the trust and respect of many soldiers and leaders.

Lelouch is known for having a very stoic personality. He never cared about schoolwork, seeing the entire thing as trivial, even though his high intelligence would make it easy for him. At one point, Shirley stated that if Lelouch applied himself in school, he could get high grades. He enjoys seeking out challenges, often playing chess against nobility. In general, Lelouch takes most day-to-day affairs with open disinterest, often not even noticing the affection of others, especially Shirley, his fellow classmate. He has a strong dislike for nobles, viewing them as tepid and "overprivileged parasites."

In battle, Lelouch is very cold and tactical. He is willing to sacrifice civilians and soldiers alike, if that is what it takes to achieve the objective. In the battle at Narita, when he created a landslide that wiped out most of the enemy forces, and indirectly, several civilians in the town below, he brushed off the civilian casualties as a simple "mathematical overestimation." He did have second thoughts when he learned that one of them was Shirley's father, but he accepted that there will always be consequences for all of his actions. He also saw no problem with collapsing a large portion of Tokyo, resulting in countless military and civilian casualties.

Many characters have noted that Lelouch is quite selfish, as his desire to remake the world into what he wants it to be comes from his desire to avenge his mother's apparent death and Nunnally's sake, however in time he realizes that this goal is not just for them, but for the entire world.

Despite his cold, calculating demeanor, and ruthlessness in battle, he can be a rather compassionate person to his friends and loved ones. To Nunnally, he is a loving older brother, and to Suzaku, a loyal friend, despite the fact that the two are enemies. Lelouch, at first glance, seems to have relatively little concern for the well-being of his subordinates, but in reality, he does care about them, seeing them as valuable allies. Though he has shown preference on occasion especially with Kallen.

    </string>
    <string name="toua">toua is a genius</string>

    <string name="johan">he is a villen</string>
</resources>
